Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Yankees Baseball
      - Radio, 1952 Apr. 30-Sept. 4 (Reel 909)
      - Radio, 1952 Sept. 4-28 (Reel 910)
      - Television, 1952 Apr.-Sept.
  - Blue Shield
    - Advancing Human Frontier, television, 1952 Oct.-Nov.
  - Johns-Manville
    - Bill Henry News, radio, 1952 Jan.-Aug.
    - Bill Henry News, radio, 1952 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 911)
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre
      - Duchess of Idaho, 1952 Jan. 7
      - Goodbye, My Fancy, 1952 Jan. 14
      - Capt. Horatio Hornblower, 1952 Jan. 21
      - Branded, 1952 Jan. 28
      - Take Care of My Little Girl, 1952 Feb. 4
      - Showboat, 1952 Feb. 11
      - Kim, 1952 Feb. 18
      - My Blue Heaven, 1952 Feb. 25
      - Young Man With a Horn, 1952 Mar. 3
      - Follow the Sun, 1952 Mar. 10
      - Top o' the Morning, 1952 Mar. 17
      - Come to the Stable, 1952 Mar. 24
      - I Can Get It for You Wholesale, 1952 Mar. 31
      - Union Station, 1952 Apr. 7
      - Royal Wedding, 1952 Apr. 14
      - The Crisis, 1952 Apr. 21
      - No Highway in the Sky, 1952 Apr. 28
      - On Moonlight Bay, 1952 May 5
      - Riding High, 1952 May 12
      - The Magnificent Yankee, 1952 May 19
      - Room for One More, 1952 May 26
    - Lux Hour of Mystery and Romance, 1952 June
    - Lux Radio Theatre
      - Adam and Evalyn, 1952 Sept. 29
      - I'll Never Forget You, 1952 Sept. 22
      - Here Comes the Groom, 1952 Sept. 15
      - Here Comes the Groom, (continued), 1952 Sept. 15 (Reel 912)
      - Two Weeks with Love, 1952 Sept. 8
      - The Model and the Marriage Broker, 1952 Oct. 6
      - Five Fingers, 1952 Oct. 13
      - My Six Convicts, 1952 Oct. 20
      - My Son John, 1952 Oct. 27
      - Viva Zapata, 1952 Nov. 3
      - Grounds for Marriage, 1952 Nov. 10
      - Submarine Command, 1952 Nov. 17
      - The Blue Veil, 1952 Nov. 24
      - King Solomon's Mines, 1952 Dec. 1
      - Strictly Dishonorable, 1952 Dec. 8
      - African Queen, 1952 Dec. 15
      - Les Miserables, 1952 Dec. 22
      - Westward the Women, 1952 Dec. 29
    - Lux Video Theatre
      - Mr. Finchley Versus the Atom Bomb, 1952 Jan. 7
      - Ceylon Treasure, 1952 Jan. 14
      - The Sound of Waves Breaking, 1952 Jan. 21
      - For Goodness Sake, 1952 Jan. 28
      - Kelly, 1952 Feb. 4
      - The Game of Chess, 1952 Feb. 11
      - Life, Liberty, and Orrin Dooley, 1952 Feb. 18
      - The Bargain, 1952 Feb. 25
      - Night Be Quiet, 1952 Mar. 3
      - The Promotion, 1952 Mar. 10
      - The Foggy, Foggy Dew, 1952 Mar. 17
      - Julie, 1952 Mar. 24
      - Taste, 1952 Mar. 31
      - Hunt the Man Down, 1952 Apr. 7
      - Decision, 1952 Apr. 14
      - Operation Weekend, 1952 Apr. 21
      - Salad Days, 1952 Apr. 28
      - Masquerade, 1952 May 5
      - Marriage in the Beginning, 1952 May 12
      - Ferry Crisis at Friday Point, 1952 May 19
      - Pattern for Glory, 1952 May 26
      - Garveau '83, 1952 June 2
      - The Lesson, 1952 June 9
      - The Lesson, (continued), 1952 June 9 (Reel 913)
      - Gilia, 1952 June 16
      - Welcome Home, Lefty, 1952 June 23
      - I Can't Remember, 1952 June 30
        [July 7 broadcast missing]
      - Son Wanted, 1952 July 14
      - The Brigadier, 1952 July 21
      - Two Pale Horsemen, 1952 July 28
      - Two Make Four, 1952 Aug. 4
      - The Orchard, 1952 Aug. 11
      - You Be the Bad Guy, 1952 Aug. 18
      - The Magnolia Touch, 1952 Aug. 25
      - The Return of Ulysses, 1952 Sept. 1
      - Ile, 1952 Sept. 8
      - Stone's Throw, 1952 Sept. 15
      - Happily But Not Forever, 1952 Sept. 22
      - A Message For Janice, 1952 Sept. 29
      - Legacy of Love, 1952 Oct. 6
        [Oct. 13 broadcast missing]
      - Country Lawyer, 1952 Oct. 20
      - Three Hours Between Planes, 1952 Oct. 27
      - The Face of Autumn, 1952 Nov. 3
      - Something to Celebrate, 1952 Nov. 10
      - The Man Who Struck It Rich, 1952 Nov. 17
      - The Hill, 1952 Nov. 24
      - Amo, Amas, Amat, 1952 Dec. 1
      - Fear, 1952 Dec. 8
      - Song for a Banjo, 1952 Dec. 15
      - A Child Is Born, 1952 Dec. 22
      - The Key, 1952 Dec. 29
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Curtain Call
      - The Promise, 1952 June 20
      - The Soul of the Great Bell, 1952 June 27
      - Azaya, 1952 July 4
      - The Party, 1952 July 18
      - Summer Evening, 1952 July 25
      - Swell Girl, 1952 Aug. 1
      - Season of Divorce, 1952 Aug. 8
      - Vexations of A.J. Wentworth, 1952 Aug. 15
      - The Liar, 1952 Aug. 22
      - The Summer People, 1952 Aug. 29
      - The Model Millionaire, 1952 Sept. 5
      - The Model Millionaire, (continued), 1952 Sept. 5 (Reel 914)
      - Mutiny in the Zoo, 1952 Sept. 12
      - Carrie Marr, 1952 Sept. 19
      - Concert in Brooklyn, 1952 Sept. 26
    - Dennis Day, 1952 Feb.-June, Oct.-Dec.
    - Ezio Pinza Show, 1952 Jan.-June
    - Meredith Willson's Music Room, 1952 June-Sept. 21
    - Meredith Willson's Music Room, 1952 Sept. (Reel 915)
    - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1952 Jan.-May, Oct.-Dec.
    - Today, 1952 June-July
  - Scott Paper Co.
    - Omnibus, 1952 Dec.
  - Swift & Co.
    - Movie Time, 1952 Jan.
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 974)
    - Delicate Story, 1951
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Foreign Intrigue, 1952
    - Home of Champions, 1952
    - Spot announcements, 1952
    - Yankees Baseball, 1952
  - Ford Motor Company (Reel 975)
    - Ford Festival
      - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5-1952 June 26
      - Mr. Peepers, 1952 July 3-Sept. 11
      - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5-1952 June 26 (Reel 976)
        [Beginning of reel fogged; done over on reel 977]
      - Mr. Peepers, 1952 July 3-Sept. 11
      - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5 (Reel 977)
      - James Melton, 1952 June 26
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Academy Award Show, 1953 Mar. 19
    - Martha Raye All Star Revue, 1953 Oct. 10
    - Dennis Day, 1953 Jan.-June, Oct.-Dec.
    - Dennis Day, 1954 Jan.-June
    - The Goldbergs, 1953 July-Sept.
    - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1953 Jan.-June
    - Tony Martin, 1953 July-Aug.
    - Your Show of Shows (Caesar/Coca), 1953 Sept.-Dec.
    - Your Show of Shows (Caesar/Coca), 1954 Jan.-May
    - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1953 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 981)
    - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1954 Jan.-Mar.
  - Johns-Manville (Reel 982)
    - Fair Meadows USA, 1951 Dec. 16-23
      [Episodes 7, 8]
    - Fair Meadows USA, 1952 Jan.-Apr.
    - Commercials, 1952
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Spot announcements, Time Savers, 1953 July 7
    - Music Report for Motion Pictures, 1953 July 8
    - Economy truck radio commercials, 1953
    - Ford TV individual dealer purchase, 1949-1950
    - Spot announcements, Houston simulcast Eastern Parkway Boxing, 1953
    - Bill Ingram News, cars, trucks, 1953
    - Used Car and Truck Service, 1953
    - Robert Trout News, car, commercials, 1952-1953
    - Shooting scripts, cars, trucks, 1953
    - Ford dealer spots, car, radio, 1953
  - Alphabetical Scripts (Reel 984)
    - Allsweet--Ballantine, 1953
    - Ballantine--Johns-Manville, 1953 (Reel 985)
    - Johns-Manville--Kraft, 1953 (Reel 986)
    - Kraft--End, 1953 (Reel 987)
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1953
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1953
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 989)
    - Radio, 1954 Mar.-Sept.
      [Includes pre-season]
    - Television, 1954 Mar.-June
    - Television, 1954 June-Sept. (Reel 990)
  - Blue Cross
    - It Seems Like Yesterday, Television, 1954
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - Racket Squad, Television, 1954
    - Sammy Kaye Show, 1954 Aug.-Dec.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre, side 1, 1954 Jan.-Feb. 25
      [Act I, II of Feb. 25 broadcast]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, side 2, 1954 Feb. 25-July 7
    - Kraft Television Theatre, side 1, 1954 July 8-Nov. 10 (Reel 991)
      [Acts I-III of Nov. 10 broadcast]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, side 2, 1954 Nov. 10-Dec.
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1954 Sept.-Dec.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1954 Jan.-June, Aug.-Sept 2
      [Acts I-III of Sept. 2 broadcast]
    - Lux Video Theatre, side 1, 1954 Sept.2-Dec. (Reel 992)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, side 1, 1954 Jan.-Oct. 26
      [Act I, II of Oct. 26 broadcast]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, side 2, 1954 Oct. 26-Dec.
  - Johns-Manville
    - Bill Henry News, 1954
  - Scott Paper Co. (Reel 999)
    - Bob Crosby Show, 1955 June-Dec.
    - Valiant Lady, 1955 Dec.
    - Omnibus, 1955 Oct.-Dec.
  - Swift & Co.
    - Garry Moore Show, 1955 Jan.-Sept.
  - Sylvania
    - Beat the Clock, 1955
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1955 Jan.-Feb.
    - Tom Corbett, Space Cadet, 1955 Jan.-Apr.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Aug.
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 1000)
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams)
    - Pond's Theatre TV
      - Erica, 1955 June 2
      - Life and Taxes, 1955 June 9
      - Mother is watching, 1955 June 16
      - The Fascinating Stranger, 1955 June 23
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - One Hill, One River, 1955 Jan. 5
      - A Bit o' Love, 1955 Jan. 6
      - Patterns, 1955 Jan. 12
      - The Written Word, 1955 Jan. 19
      - Boy Will Be Boys, 1955 Jan. 26
      - The Skin Game, 1955 Feb. 2
      - Patterns, (repeat), 1955 Feb. 9
      - Departure, 1955 Feb. 16
      - The Emperor Jones, 1955 Feb. 23
      - Half the World's a Bride, 1955 Mar. 2
      - The Night Watchers, 1955 Mar. 9
      - Jeannie, 1955 Mar. 16
      - The Story of Mary Surratt, 1955 Mar. 23
      - Southwest Corner, 1955 Mar. 30
      - Whim of Iron, 1955 Apr. 6
      - Now Where Was I, 1955 Apr. 13
      - Gramercy Ghost, 1955 Apr. 20
      - A Seacoast in Bohemia, 1955 Apr. 27
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams)
    - Pond's Theatre TV
      - Coquette, 1955 July 7
      - The Hickory Limb, 1955 Jan. 13
      - The Rugged Mountains, 1955 Jan. 20
      - The Cornered Man, 1955 Jan. 27
      - Thirty, Honey, Thirty, 1955 Feb. 3
      - Prologue to Glory, 1955 Feb. 10
      - The Dover Road, 1955 Feb. 17
      - Joe Landry's Kid, 1955 Feb. 24
      - Anna Christie, 1955 Mar. 3
      - Billy Budd, 1955 Mar. 10
      - The Silver Box, 1955 Mar. 17
      - Autumn Crocus, 1955 Mar. 24
      - The Forger, 1955 Mar. 31
      - The Glass Parlor, 1955 Apr. 7
      - No Riders, 1955 Apr. 14
      - Thunder Rock, 1955 Apr. 21
      - Hang Up My Guns, 1955 Apr. 28
      - Candle Light, 1955 May 5
      - Cynara, 1955 May 12
      - The Ways of Courage, 1955 May 19
      - The Kingdom of Andrew Jones, 1955 May 26
      - Death is a Spanish Dancer, 1955 June 20
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company (Reel 1001)
    - Sammy Kaye Show, 1955 Jan.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Music Hall, Rudy Vallee, radio, 1955 Feb.-Sept.
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Ford Star Jubilee
      - The Caine Mutiny Court Marshal, 1955 Nov. 19
      - Television, 1955 Sept.-Dec.
  - J.P. French Co.
    - The World of Mr. Sweeney, Television, 1955 Jan.-June
  - CIBA
    - Medical Horizons, Television, 1955 Sept.-Dec.
  - AllSweet
    - The Garry Moore Show, Television, 1955 Jan.-June
  - Chun King
    - The Garry Moore Show, Television, 1955
  - Blue Cross
    - Bill Leonard News, Six O'Clock Report, television, 1955 Feb.-May
      [Some missing]
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - Racket Squad, 1955
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1955 Jan.-June
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Jan.-July
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - Number Four with Flowers, 1955 Nov. 2
      - Ticket and the Tempest, 1955 Nov. 9
      - Day of Judgment, 1955 Nov. 23
      - Once a Genius, 1955 Nov. 30
      - My Lady Ruth, 1955 Dec. 7
      - A Nugget from the Sunset, 1955 Dec. 15
      - Christmas Dinner, 1955 Dec. 21
      - Eleven O'Clock Flight, 1955 Dec. 23
  - Lever Brothers (Reel 1002)
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Mar.-Apr.
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - TV Star Tonight
      - You Need Me, 1955 Feb. 3
      - Weekend, 1955 Feb. 10
      - Concerning Death, 1955 Feb. 17
      - How Beautiful with Shoes, 1955 Feb. 24
      - Zone of Quiet, 1955 Mar. 3
      - Ile, 1955 Mar. 10
      - The Murderer, 1955 Mar. 17
      - A Matter of Life, 1955 Mar. 24
      - Death of a Stranger, 1955 Mar. 31
      - Treasure Trove, 1955 Apr. 7
      - The Lavender Kite, 1955 Apr. 14
      - The Giants Stair, 1955 Apr. 21
      - Zero Hour, 1955 Apr. 28
      - The Dark Search, 1955 May 5
      - The College Hour, 1955 May 12
      - Tender Roots, 1955 May 19
      - Golden Victory, 1955 May 26
      - Taste, 1955 June 2
      - Wanted: Poor Boy, 1955 June 9
      - Strength of Steel, 1955 June 16
      - Cross-Words, 1955 June 23
      - The Gallant Lady, 1955 June 30
      - Footfalls, 1955 July 7
      - The Critic, 1955 July 14
      - The Kewpie Doll, 1955 July 21
      - The Matrimony Shop, 1955 July 28
      - Edge of Light, 1955 Aug. 4
      - The Ring of General Macias, 1955 Aug. 11
      - The Prom, 1955 Aug. 18
      - Flame and Ice, 1955 Aug. 25
      - Trifles, 1955 Sept. 1
      - Success Story, 1955 Sept. 8
      - Long Distance, 1955 Sept. 15
      - Visitation, 1955 Sept. 22
      - The Terrible Woman, 1955 Sept. 29
      - Not for Me, 1955 Oct. 6
      - One Day More, 1955 Oct. 13
      - The Little Wife, 1955 Oct. 20
      - Finders Keepers, 1955 Oct. 27
      - Night Be Quiet, 1955 Nov. 3
      - The Ryan Girl, 1955 Nov. 10
      - The Cage, 1955 Nov. 17
      - Have Faith in Your Agent, 1955 Nov. 24
      - The Summer Road, 1955 Dec. 1
      - Nightmare By Day, 1955 Dec. 8
      - Gang-Up, 1955 Dec. 15
      - The Selfish Giant, 1955 Dec. 22
      - Write Me a Love Scene, 1955 Dec. 29
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - Hang Up My Guns, 1957 Jan. 2
      - Six Hours of Terror, 1957 Jan. 9
      - No Warning, 1957 Jan. 16
      - Most Blessed Woman, 1957 Jan. 23
      - The Singin' Idol, 1957 Jan. 30
      - The Discoverers, 1957 Feb. 6
      - The Man Who Couldn't Say No, 1957 Feb. 13
      - Give Me the Courage, 1957 Feb. 20
      - A Traveller from Brussels, 1957 Feb. 27
      - The Duel, 1957 Mar. 6
      - Collision, 1957 Mar. 13
      - Night of the Plague, 1957 Mar. 20
      - Sheriff's Man, 1957 Mar. 27
      - The Medallion, 1957 Apr. 3
      - A Matter of Life, 1957 Apr. 17
      - A Night of Rain, 1957 Apr. 24
      - Drummer Man, 1957 May 1
      - Flesh and Blood, 1957 May 8
      - The Glass Wall, 1957 May 15
      - Men of Prey, 1957 May 22
      - All Those Beautiful Girls, 1957 May 29
      - The Roaring 20th, 1957 June 5
      - Fire and Ice, 1957 June 12
      - Nothing Personal, 1957 June 19
      - The Curly-Headed Kid, 1957 June 26
      - Flowers for 2B, 1955 May 4
      - Judge Contains Hotel, 1955 May 11
      - The Braveness of Christy Fallon, 1955 May 18
      - The Million Dollar Rookie, 1955 May 25
      - A Woman for Tony, 1955 June 1
      - Someone to Hang, 1955 June 8
      - My Aunt Daisy, 1955 June 15
      - Drop on the Devil, 1955 June 22
      - The Mob, 1955 June 29
      - Impasse, 1955 July 6
      - The Straw, 1955 July 13 (Reel 1003)
      - In the LaBanza, 1955 July 20
      - Meet a Body, 1955 July 27
      - Spur of the Moment, 1955 Aug. 3
      - Two Times Two, 1955 Aug. 10
      - The Failure, 1955 Aug. 17
      - Haunted, 1955 Aug. 24
      - The Chess Game, 1955 Aug. 31
      - Woman of Principle, 1955 Sept. 7
      - It's Only Money, 1955 Sept. 14
      - The King's Bounty, 1955 Sept. 21
      - The Diamond As Big As the Ritz, 1955 Sept. 28
      - The Beautiful Time, 1955 Oct. 5
      - Trucks Welcome, 1955 Oct. 12
      - I, Mrs. Bibb, 1955 Oct. 19
      - One, 1955 Oct. 26
      - In Albert's Room, 1953 Aug. 19
  - [Sponsor unidentified]
    - Believe It Or Not
      - Wheels of Chance, 1950 Feb. 1
      - The Case of the Missing Model, (Directors's copy), 1950 Feb. 15
      - The Diamond Eye, (Directors's copy), 1950 Feb. 22
      - Journey Through Darkness, (Directors's copy), 1950 Mar. 1
      - Murder to Come, (Directors's copy), 1950 Mar. 8
      - Cross of Valor, (Directors's copy), 1950 Mar. 15
      - The Mystery of the Missing Guest, 1950 May 10
      - The Bodark Tree, (Directors's copy), 1950 May 18
      - The Silent Witness, (Directors's copy), 1950 May 25
      - Passage to Zermatt, (Directors's copy), 1950 June 1
      - Death Calls the Tune, (Directors's copy), 1950 June 8
      - The Million Dollar Corpse, (Directors's copy), 1950 July 6
      - Double Jeopardy, (Directors's copy), 1950 July 13
      - Murder With a Payoff, 1950 July 27
      - Loser Take All, (Directors's copy), 1950 Aug. 3
      - The Ghostly Will, (Directors's copy), 1950 Aug. 10
      - Corpus Delecti, (Directors's copy), 1950 Aug. 17
      - The Emerald Tattoo, (Directors's copy), 1950 Aug. 24
      - The Blood Call, 1950 Aug. 31
  - Chun King
    - The Garry Moore Show, television, 1956 Jan.-Sept.
      [Episodes missing]
  - Lever Brothers
    - Arthur Godfrey, television, 1956 Jan.-Mar.
  - CIBA
    - Medical Horizons, television, 1956 Jan.-Mar., Oct.
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Ford Star Jubilee, television, 1956
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1956 Aug.-Dec.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - The Thieving Magpies, 1956 Jan. 4
      - The Sears Girls, 1956 Jan. 11
      - The Devil as a Roaring Lion, 1956 Jan. 18
      - Home Is the Hero, 1956 Jan. 25
      - Five Minutes To Live, 1956 Feb. 2
      - Good Old Charlie Faye, 1956 Feb. 8
      - The Man on Roller Skates, 1956 Feb. 15
      - The Man on Roller Skates, (continued), 1956 Feb. 15 (Reel 1004)
      - Snapfinger Creek, 1956 Feb. 22
      - Bobbie, 1956 Feb. 29
      - The Fool Killer, 1956 Mar. 7
      - The Lost Weekend, 1956 Mar. 21
      - A Night To Remember, 1956 Mar. 28
      - Paper Foxhole, 1956 Apr. 4
      - The Lost Shadow, 1956 Apr. 11
      - No Riders, 1956 Apr. 18
      - The Gentle Grafter, 1956 Apr. 24
      - A Night To Remember, 1956 May 2
      - Death is a Spanish Dancer, 1956 May 9
      - A Profile in Courage, 1956 May 16
      - Bed Room 12 on the Appalachian Waterfall, 1956 May 23
      - Box Seven-O-Four, 1956 May 30
      - The Night of May Third, 1956 June 6
      - Boy In a Cage, 1956 June 13
      - Flying Object at 3 O'Clock High, 1956 June 20
      - Starfish, 1956 June 27
      - Tear Open the Skies, 1956 July 4
      - The Long Arm, 1956 July 11
      - Babies For Sale, 1956 July 18
      - Prairie Night, 1956 July 25
      - One Way West, 1956 Aug. 1
      - Anna Santonello, 1956 Aug. 8
      - The Girl Who Saw Too Much, 1956 Aug. 29
      - Mock Trial, 1956 Sept. 5
      - Shadow of Evil, 1956 Sept. 12
      - Out to Kill, 1956 Sept. 19
      - The Plunge, 1956 Sept. 26
      - The Life of Mickey Mantle, 1956 Oct. 3
      - Murder of a Sand Flea, 1956 Oct. 10
      - I Am 15--And I Don't Want to Die, 1956 Oct. 17
      - The Grapefruits to Lisbon, 1956 Oct. 24
      - Hit and Run, 1956 Oct. 31
      - Shadow of Suspicion, 1956 Nov. 7
      - Before It's Too Late, 1956 Nov. 14
      - The Day of the Hunter, 1956 Nov. 21
      - Time Lock, (missing), 1956 Nov. 28
      - The Ninth Hour, 1956 Dec. 5
      - Teddy Bear, 1956 Dec. 12
      - The Wonderful Gift, (missing), 1956 Dec. 19
      - The Just and the Unjust, 1956 Dec. 26
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - TV Star Tonight
      - The Big Fifteenth, 1956 Jan. 5
      - With Glory and Honor, 1956 Jan. 12
      - A Night Visitor, 1956 Jan. 19
      - Early Frost, 1956 Jan. 26
      - Below Average, 1956 Feb. 2
      - The Happy Journey, 1956 Feb. 9
      - The Thing That Never Happened, 1956 Feb. 16
      - Rite of Love, 1956 Feb. 23
      - Three Hours Between Planes, 1956 Mar. 1
      - Night Escape, 1956 Mar. 8
      - Love Is A Lawyer, 1956 Mar. 15
      - The Chevigny Man, 1956 Mar. 22
      - Boy Crazy, 1956 Mar. 29
      - Two Windows, 1956 Apr. 5
      - A Door You Can Close, 1956 Apr. 12
      - An Ambulance for Jill, 1956 Apr. 19
      - Tough Boy, 1956 Apr. 26
      - Can You Coffee Pot On Skates, 1956 May 3
      - The Girl, 1956 May 10
      - A Trip To Czardis, 1956 May 17
      - Have Faith and Have Patience, 1956 May 24
      - Kingdom's Child, 1956 May 31
      - A Small Glass Bottle, 1956 June 7
      - The Long View, 1956 June 14
      - The Ascent of P.J. O'Hara, 1956 June 21
      - Mr. Bell's Creation, 1956 June 28
      - Shadow of Evil, 1956 July 5
      - The Coffee Shop Incident, 1956 July 12
      - Blood Call, 1956 July 19
      - Will Power, 1956 July 26
      - The Gentleman Caller, 1956 Aug. 2
      - The Mirthmakers, 1956 Aug. 9
    - Racket Squad, 1956 Jan.-Aug.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1956 Jan.-Feb.
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1956 Mar.-Aug. (Reel 1005)
  - CIBA
    - Medical Horizons
      - 2. Beyond the Mask, 1956 Sept. 16
      - 4. One Out of Ten, 1956 Sept. 30
      - 8. Most Happy Time, 1956 Oct. 28
      - 6. Man Under Sea, 1956 Oct. 14
      - 12. Happy Children, 1956 Nov. 25
      - 12. Happy Children, (continued), 1956 Nov. 25 (Reel 1006)
      - 10. Kine, 1956 Nov. 11
      - 16. Christmas in Community Hospital, 1956 Dec. 23
      - 14. Bone Engineering, 1956 Dec. 9
      - 18. The Hidden Disease, 1957 Jan. 6
      - 20. When Emergency Strikes, 1957 Jan. 20
      - 22. Report on Cancer, 1957 Feb. 3
      - 23. High Blood Pressure, 1957 Feb. 10
      - 25. Operation CVA, 1957 Feb. 24
      - 27. Radiology, 1957 Mar. 10
      - 29. Psychosomatic Med, 1957 Mar. 24
      - 31. Deafness, 1957 Apr. 7
      - 33. A Triumph and a Challenge, 1957 Apr. 21
      - 35. Legal Medicine, 1957 May 5
      - 37. Burns, 1957 May 19
      - 39. Radiology, 1957 June 2
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1957 Mar.-Aug.
  - Swift & Co.
    - Swift's Movie Time, 1951 Oct.-1952 Jan.
  - Eastman Kodak (Reel 1007)
    - Kodak Family Adventure
      - College Episode, undated
      - Baseball Hall of Fame, undated
      - Roots--Boston, undated
      - Martha's Vineyard Story, undated
      - The Newport Story, undated
      - The Old Flames, undated
      - Indiana University Story, undated
      - Riverdale Revisited, undated
      - Little Red Schoolhouse, undated
      - The Chicago Story, undated
      - Betty Discovers Wisconsin, undated
      - The Iowa Story, undated
      - The Natchez Recluse, undated
      - Teddy and the Shanty-Boaters, undated
      - The Teche County and Avery Island, undated
      - Barbara and the Touring Players, undated
      - Initiation, undated
      - Hermit of Berthoud Pass, undated
      - The Capistrano Pigeon, undated
      - The San Francisco Story, undated
      - Road Black, undated
      - Pay-Dirt, undated
      - The Klamath Falls Story, undated
      - The North Carolina Story, undated
      - The Charleston Story, undated
      - Florida Fish Story, undated
      - Basic Story Outline, undated
      - Character Descriptions: Jim, undated
      - Character Descriptions: Betty, undated
      - Character Descriptions: Barbara, undated
      - Character Descriptions: Teddy, undated
      - Table of Contents, undated
      - The Summons Home, undated
      - America Discovers the Osbornes, undated
      - The 86th Floor, undated
      - Shopping Trip, undated
      - Four Rooms with a View, undated
      - The Brooklyn Story, undated
      - The Old House, undated
      - An Act of Congress, undated
      - The Gettysburg Story, undated
      - The Osbornes Go House-Hunting, undated
      - The New House, undated
      - The Osborne Crisis, undated
      - The Ben Franklin Desk, undated
      - Teddy and the Magician, undated
      - Foreword--Role of Picture Taking, undated
      - Diplomatic Incident, undated